[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, what I can see, Piers, is that the eastern part of the country seems to be under the control of anti-Gadhafi forces.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "And we could see a completely different situation to the one we saw in Egypt, couldn't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tripoli"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Did you know if this is true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "What we're hearing from people here is that, indeed, that was the case in Tripoli.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Well, currently, or the past couple of days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, currently first, and then maybe give me an overview of what you believe is the bigger picture here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "I mean how many people do you think are getting killed here, Adam?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "It's tough to say, honestly, because you hear a lot of numbers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Do they have the persistence, do you think, to go through with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I truly believe they do, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "If you're an American watching this, what should you be thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "LITZER: Well, you should be thinking, first of all, about the young people who are going to die.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "But if you're at the White House and you're making the call here, if this all kicks off in the way some fear it may and we're seeing widespread attacks on the people of Libya, should America intervene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I don't think America should intervene by itself, but it wouldn't be out of the question to see an international coalition get together and do something to try to stop the bloodshed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["Libya", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "What are the Europeans going to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I think it's a fascinating dilemma for all European governments right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Europe", "Europe", "Italy"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Big calls for these politicians right now, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "There's enormous ramifications for the people of Europe, southern Europe, Italy, especially, but all of those countries are going to watch this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Where will it end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Well, I mean, you know, if I knew, boy, I'd be in that next spot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "That's a major escalation, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Oh, it's huge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Shouldn't we be encouraging and supporting what we're witnessing here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "We should.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Christchurch", "New Zealand"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "How bad has this earthquake been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Yes, we're starting to get reports out of the city of Christchurch, which is in the south islands of New Zealand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["Tripoli"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What are you hearing from your sources in Libya?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, what I'm hearing is that Gadhafi is using the air force, using helicopters, bombing Tripoli.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "How far will he go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, good evening, Mr. Morgan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "I mean how bad would it get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Well, I believe we've heard his son Saif say that we're going to go down to the last bullet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What kind of man is he in private when you meet him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Just like every other politician.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Can I please -- can I come in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Gentlemen, thank you all very much for your time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What is your view of that decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Well, he allegedly had terminal prostate cancer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Do you think you'll ever get any kind of peace or justice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "UDSON: I think now there's a very excellent opportunity for the full truth to come out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Victoria, is there anything he could do now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, justice has been denied to all of us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "What -- Paul, I was going to ask you, what do you believe prompted the attack on that flight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Well, we don't know for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Why did you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Well, it was the terms of the -- the settlement had been offered to the families as a no-fault settlement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "With all of your experience, where do you see this going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Well, I think the bottom line is that this regime is doomed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", ":", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "What can the west do collectively to try to get involved here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I think a first step, it's absolutely crucial that President Obama now come out and state very clearly that the United States is on the side of the Libyan people in this fight, to rally the international community, at least the civilized world to that -- to that call for action.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "And if he does go, where would he end up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I wouldn't take it for granted that the regime is going to crumble.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["America", "Middle East"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "How would you position Gadhafi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "I would say that there was clearly, for a long time, several decades, Gadhafi was, in fact, something of America's public enemy number one in the Middle East.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "CC", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Where do you see this developing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "In the long term, Piers, it's good news for the economy, in the sense it will be a balanced and more stable economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Tom Kloza, would you agree with that assessment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Well, I'd agree with it in the short term.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Kloza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "If that was to happen, that could have a very negative impact on the American economy, couldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "It could.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "How important has the Internet and social networking been in Libya, compared to the other uprisings we've seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "I think the fact that the country shut down the Internet and telecom within the country shows that it was very important.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "It's not necessarily just because the Internet exists?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Jasmine Revolution"], "LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "What are you hearing about China, and whether we can see similar uprisings there, fueled by the Internet and social networking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I think the key is not the fact that this jasmine -- China's Jasmine Revolution failed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}]